Amey Jeurkar jeurkaramey@ gmail.com +91 8669049754

linkedin.com/in/ameyjeurkar-3a7476137/

Amey Jeurkar

Software Engineer

About me

An engineer with 1 years of experience working prominently with frontend technologies like React.Js and Angular Framework. Built product critical features respecting project timelines and engineering standards. Also contributed in demos on several occasions.

Software Development Skills

Programming Languages and Frameworks

Java, HTML, CSS, React.Js, Angular, Node.Js, Express.Js, NoSQL

Tools & Infrastructure

MongoDB, Git

Work Experience

Application Development Associate, Accenture, December 2020 - present

- 1. Worked with the Poles & Towers team– Built completely responsive application for Poles while also enhancing user experience for both mobile & desktop users
- 2. A responsive design with smooth experience over different browsers
- 3. Developing & maintaining UI

Intern, Tata Consultancy Services, December 2019 - July 2020

- 1. Redesigned user interface for better user experience & performance in Angular
- 2. Developed UX designs using AdobeXD tools
- 3. Worked under the guidance of Mr. Advait Upadeo on developing an IoT application

Projects

SIP Calculator using React & Chart.Js

This application makes use of Chart.Js library for better understanding of how much return user can expect over invested amount.

Converting excel to legible Questionnaire app using React & XLSX library

Built a mobile application which shows excelsheet data in more readable manner making it easier for the user to read it.

Job Portal using MERN Stack

This application lets user perform the CRUD operations from creation, updation and deletion of job profiles.

Hangman Game using React

It's a guessing game where players are required to guess the correct programming language or they lose.

Education

Yeshwantrao Chavan College of Engineering, Nagpur, 2016-2020Bachelor's Degree in Computer Technology Engineering, GPA 7.18/10

Achievements / Extra Curricular Activities

- 1. Awarded "Award of Excellence" consecutively between 2019-2020
- 2. Conducted workshops on Android Development
- 3. Head of Hospitality Management Team for Computer Technology branch.